

# **CONTACTS**



+37068127238



arnoldasstrukcinskas@gmail.com



Kaunas



LinkedIn profile



My Projects

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

- JAVA basics, OOP
- Create and work with websites using Spring Boot
- Work with **MySQL** databases
- Creation of Android applications using Java
- Version control using **GitHub**

# **EXPERIENCE**

Pool technician-lifeguard UAB "Eglės" sanatorija 2021-07 - now

Car fleet maintenance Citybee, UAB "PrimeLeasing" 2021-04 - 2021-12

Physiotherapist UAB "Eglės" sanatorija 2018-07 - 2021-07

# **LANGUAGES**

- Lithuanian (Native)
- English (B2)
- Russian (C)

# ARNOLDAS STRUKČINSKAS

Junior Java Back-End developer

# **ABOUT ME**

After graduating, I successfully worked as a physiotherapist for several years. For a number of years, I was one of the most valued specialists of my clients, but I was missing something. Therefore, I remembered my teenage interest in programming and started learning on my own. While I was studying, the desire to learn something new - grew, so I successfully completed Vilnius Coding School Java course. I am actively expanding my knowledge in the field of programming. My goals include continuous improvement and skill development, especially in working with Java. My skills includes problem-solving, teamwork, and a passionate desire to progress. Currently, I am seeking opportunities that will allow me to continue learning and growing in my professional career.

# **EDUCATION**

#### JAVA course

Vilniaus Coding School

2023-07-14 - 2023-09-13, 2 months 160 hours

During the course I learned strong Java basics, learned to create/work with projects using Spring Boot, work with data using MySQL, create android applications using Java, use GitHub and Docker platforms.

#### Link to my project:

https://github.com/arnoldasstrukcinskas/medziagu\_skaiciuokle.git

## Java Programming Masterclass updated to Java 17

Udemy.com

2023-11, 20h

During this course I learned how to create Java applications with IntelliJ. Java basics and object oriented programing.

#### C# Basics for Beginners: Learn C# Fundamentals by Coding

Udemy.com

2023-04, 5,5h

During this course I learned strong C# basics working with variables, loops, arrays and files. Also during this course I was reading "The C# player's guide" by RB Whitaker, where i learned basics of C# object oriented programming, generics, and collections.

## Sports physiotherapy master's degree

2019 - 2021

Lithuanian university of health sciences

## Physiotherapy bachelor's degree

2015 - 2019

Lithuanian university of health sciences